Privacy policy
--------------

Updated: April 25th 2023

**1\. General**

You may visit DealDash.com at any time without registering. When you visit our website, data is saved on our servers, as is the website that you visit us from, the advertising you may have been referred by, the websites that you proceed to from our site, the type of browser you use, and your IP address.

As this is being done, no personal data is directly associated with you. However, we do need some personal information from you if you want to actively participate in DealDash.com or use our mobile applications.

Once you have registered with DealDash.com, you are asked to choose a DealDash.com user name together with a password, which then allows you to take advantage of all of the DealDash.com services.

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.dealdash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

You can revoke your consent any time by closing your account with us. For requests and inquiries related to California Consumer Privacy Act, please refer to section 7.

**2\. What Data Do We Collect?**

"Personal data" is the information that readily identifies you, for example your name, address, e-mail address and mobile phone number or your payment details. When you register, personal data is recorded and processed by DealDash.com, as well as when you use the service, for example:

* when you purchase bids;
* when you place bids, win an auction, or purchase through Buy It Now;
* when you securely login.

"Usage data" is personal data that identify the user, as well as information on the DealDash.com services the user utilizes, for example your DealDash.com user name together with the associated password and your IP address when you purchase bids, login to the site or win an auction. It may also include things like the frequency and analysis of your auction participation and auctions you view online but do not participate in.

Dealdash.com may also collect information from you when you search, participate in a contest or questionnaire or communicate with our customer support.

We collect this data to make it possible for you to use DealDash.com and to help us personalize and continually improve your DealDash.com experience. We maintain all data in the US and Canada ourselves and with the assistance of service providers.

Dealdash.com is directed toward a general audience over the age of 18 and is specifically not directed toward children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have information about anyone under 13, we will promptly delete it.

**3\. Use of the Data**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized DealDash.com experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

* provide the services and customer support you request;
* resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems;
* prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use;
* customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
* tell you about our services, targeted marketing, site updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences.

**4\. Newsletter**

When you register with DealDash.com, you are added to receive the email newsletter. You may unsubscribe at anytime from the newsletter and other marketing communications by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter emails.

**5\. Sharing Personal Data to Third Parties**

We will not share your personal information with third parties for that recipient’s own purposes unless you have clearly consented to such sharing. We will share your data with service providers who assist us with the site, marketing and our operations, such as payment processing or post-purchase fulfillment.

DealDash.com may also share your data for law enforcement purposes, to protect our business from fraud or abuse, or in the event another party purchases our company or assets.

**6\. Viewing/Changing Personal Data**

You can view the information in your DealDash.com account at any time and update it as necessary using your DealDash.com user name and your DealDash.com password. You can also at any time contact our Customer Service to update your information.

Once we are informed, we will adjust incorrect data accordingly.

We will notify you upon request at any time as to whether and what personal data in respect to your identity or your pseudonym has been stored.

**7\. Privacy Rights of California Residents**

California law requires that we provide you a summary of your privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (the "Act") and the California Civil Code.

Subject to certain limits under California Civil Code if you are a California resident, you may ask us to provide you with a list of certain categories of personal information (as defined in the Civil Code) that has been collected, or that we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes and the identity of the third parties that received personal information from us for their direct marketing purposes. The Act further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. For inquiries or requests, please contact us by phone, email, or standard mail to the addresses below.

DealDash  
11670 Fountains Drive, Suite 200  
Maple Grove, MN 55369  

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.dealdash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Toll free phone: (855) 455-3325

When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what personally identifiable information your request is related to. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice."

**8\. Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account**

To the extent required by applicable statutes, you can revoke your consent to our storage, collection and processing of your personal data at any time.

You can delete your data and deactivate your DealDash.com account at any time. To delete your account, email [\[email protected\]](https://www.dealdash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or navigate to Settings > Delete account in the Android or iOS app. DealDash may retain data as required for regulatory or customer service purposes or purposes defined in the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

If you choose to close your account, all remaining bids will be destroyed.

**9\. The Use of Cookies and other identifiers**

DealDash.com uses so-called "cookies", which are text files that are stored on your computer that we retrieve when you visit the site to assist in customizing your experience with the online service.

The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your bids placed, auctions, etc.

It is necessary to accept cookies in order to use our service properly, although you may always adjust the way your browser handles cookies.

We would like to point out that turning off the ability of your browser to accept cookies may result in limited functionality.

DealDash uses first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to your site and DealDash’s advertising efforts. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.

By adjusting the privacy and security settings on your device or browser, you can manage how your mobile device and mobile browser share information, as well as how your mobile browser handles Cookies and other tracking identifiers. Please refer to instructions provided by your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.

**10\. Security Measures**

The information in your DealDash.com account and in your DealDash.com profile is password protected.

Please do not provide your log in credentials to anyone else, as you will be liable for the activity in your account.

DealDash.com will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request.

Please remember to log out of your account and to close your Internet browser window when you leave the DealDash.com site; this is especially important if you use the site through a public or shared device.

You are responsible for protecting the secrecy of your log in details, and we assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used. Let us know immediately if the secrecy of your log in credentials has been compromised. While we take reasonable steps to protect your personal data in our control, no system is foolproof.

**11\. Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, without prior notification. If we make a material change to this policy, we will highlight this to you.

We have updated our privacy policy effective April 25th, 2023. A summary of changes can be found below:

* We clarified the different ways a user can request account deletion.

We have updated our privacy policy effective December 31st, 2019. A summary of changes can be found below:

* We clarified use of Cookies and other tracking technologies, and how some devices or software may allow you to limit such technologies.
* We updated our contact details.
* We clarified how and why customer data is retained.
* We added a notification for California residents regarding their rights under the California law.
